<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Casino Gambling News</title><link>http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/index.jsp</link><description>Casino gambling news from around the world.</description><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 2011 - Casino Gambling Web, Ltd. - All Rights Reserved.</copyright><pubDate>15 Apr 2011 10:41:30 GMT</pubDate><webMaster>webmaster @ casinogamblingweb.com</webMaster><item>
<title>
Isle Of Capri To Join Casino Smorgasbord In Pennsylvania
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/isle_of_capri_to_join_casino_smorgasbord_in_pennsylvania_56763.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Isle of Capri has won the rights to the final casino license in Pennsylvania, assuring that the state with the swiftest growing gaming industry will grow even further in the near future.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Pansy Ho Could Be On Her Way Out Of Macau Casino Industry
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/pansy_ho_could_be_on_her_way_out_of_macau_casino_industry_56760.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Stanley Ho was the pioneer of casino gambling in Macau, but it appears as though his daughter, Pansy, may have her sights set on other areas of the world. The younger Ho agreed to a deal to give MGM a majority stake in their Macau partnership.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Cincinnati Casino Developer Waiting For Decision From Governor
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/cincinnati_casino_developer_waiting_for_decision_from_governor_56756.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
A good thing for the city of Cincinnati and the state of Ohio may turn bad with casino developer Rock Gaming waiting on a tax decision by Governor John Kasich.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Atlantic City Casino Gambling Revenue Continues Meltdown In March
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/atlantic_city_casino_gambling_revenue_continues_meltdown_in_march_56755.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
In what has now become a disturbing trend among casino executives in Atlantic City, revenue dropped again for their gaming establishments in March. The decline has Pennsylvania and New York feeling good about their chances.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Anti-Casino Groups In Philadelphia Encouraged By Foxwoods Move
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/anti_casino_groups_in_philadelphia_encouraged_by_foxwoods_move_56749.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Anti-casino groups in Philadelphia insist that the city does not need another casino. The decision of Philadelphia Entertainment & Development Partners to appeal the revocation of their gaming license has enthused casino opponents.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Emotions Run High As Vancouver Casino Hearings Continue
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/emotions_run_high_as_vancouver_casino_hearings_continue_56746.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Emotions ran high today when the Vancouver City Council continued its hearing on a proposed casino near B.C. Place. The hearing had many pro-casino groups fighting for approval.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Entertainment And Gambling Coming Together With Mississippi Casino
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/entertainment_and_gambling_coming_together_with_mississippi_casino_56742.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Jimmy Buffett has already made his name in the music industry, and now he is conquering the gaming industry one casino resort at a time. Mississippi regulators on Thursday approved Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville Casino & Restaurant.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Chicago Casino Helping Unemployment Rate With 1,000 Jobs
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/chicago_casino_helping_unemployment_rate_with_1_000_jobs_56741.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Showing again that the casino industry has been a major factor in bringing the nation out of the economic recession, Rivers Casino, which will open this summer in Illinois, held a job fair Friday to fill 1,000 jobs.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Genting Casinos Laying Off Over Seventy Employees In The UK
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/genting_casinos_laying_off_over_seventy_employees_in_the_uk_56734.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Showing that the US is not the only country where competition within the casino gambling industry is getting intense, Genting Casinos UK has announced that they are laying off over seventy employees.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Judges Left Out In The Cold With Greenbrier Closing Down Gambling
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/judges_left_out_in_the_cold_with_greenbrier_closing_down_gambling_56735.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Judges and lawyers are among the millions of Americans that enjoy casino gambling, but the nearly 1,000 that will be heading to West Virginia for a conference will be unable to enjoy the casino offerings of The Greenbrier.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Casino Resort Bill May Make Florida The Las Vegas Of The Southeast
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/casino_resort_bill_may_make_florida_the_las_vegas_of_the_southeast_56723.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
A casino resorts bill that originally failed to make it out of committee in Florida has passed the second time around. The legislation would make Florida the gaming capital of the East Coast.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
With Lockout Looming, Casino Accuses Vrabel Of Stealing
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/with_lockout_looming_casino_accuses_vrabel_of_stealing_56721.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
NFL players must really be feeling the crunch of a pending lockout. On Monday, NFLPA Representative Mike Vrabel, a linebacker for the Kansas City Chiefs, was arrested on a felony theft charge.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Gambling Smoking Ban Exceptions Causing Problems In Michigan
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/gambling_smoking_ban_exceptions_causing_problems_in_michigan_56720.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Lawmakers may have thought that the public would go along with the hypocrisy of allowing casinos to be exempt from a state smoking ban, but a local bar owner is one of many Michigan residents who is crying foul.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Awareness And Financial Relief Coming From US Poker Tournaments
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/awareness_and_financial_relief_coming_from_us_poker_tournaments_56718.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Pro-gambling groups have been arguing for years that the industry can do more good than harm in a community, and there are thousands of charity poker events held annually in the US that exemplify that point.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Ohio Shows Once Gambling Ball Starts Rolling, It Is Hard To Stop
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/ohio_shows_once_gambling_ball_starts_rolling_it_is_hard_to_stop_56713.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
An interesting phenomenon has started to take place across the US. Lawmakers are becoming more addicted to gambling than any person that has ever placed a bet inside a casino.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Macau Gambling Revenue Shows Online Regulations Are Needed In US
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/macau_gambling_revenue_shows_online_regulations_are_needed_in_us_56714.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Macau gambling revenue continued to soar to never before seen heights in March, and it has some analysts believing now more than ever that the US needs online gambling regulations.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
US Casinos Racking Up Millions In Underage Gambling Fines
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/us_casinos_racking_up_millions_in_underage_gambling_fines_56710.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
US casinos have a hard time policing underage gambling and they are paying a big price for that inefficiency. Casinos around the country have been fined over $1 million in the past five years for underage gambling offenses.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Casino Revenue Is Good, But What Will States Do With The Money?
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/casino_revenue_is_good_but_what_will_states_do_with_the_money__56708.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Casino advocates are happy across the US with the addition of hundreds of new facilities in recent years. The key for lawmakers, however, will be figuring out what programs to save with the additional tax revenue.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
MGM China Looks To Capitalize On Sands' Stock Instability
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/mgm_china_looks_to_capitalize_on_sands_stock_instability_56706.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Gaming companies are always looking for an opening to move into new stock exchanges and MGM Mirage may have found theirs. With controversy surrounding Las Vegas Sands and their China arm, Sands China, MGM is preparing a Hong Kong IPO.
]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Gomes Cleaning House At Resorts Leads To Lawsuit Against Casino
</title>
<link>
http://www.casinogamblingweb.com/gambling-news/casino-gambling/gomes_cleaning_house_at_resorts_leads_to_lawsuit_against_casino_56704.html
</link>
<description><![CDATA[
Dennis Gomes vowed to go after a younger clientele when he took over as the owner of Resorts Casino Hotel. The casino has recently fired middle-aged women who did not look sexy enough in their new work attire, and that has led to a lawsuit.
]]></description>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>

