<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <channel>
<atom:link href="http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   <title>Gambling Teachers Blog. Learn to Win by Pros, 300+ lessons at free learning center</title>
   <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html</link>
   <description>Gambling Teachers Blog. Learn to Win and How to Play Programs for casino and skills games with 300+ lessons taught by gambling pros. Free Learning Center for casino players.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <category domain = "http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html#">Gambling Teachers</category>
   <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 03:19:11 GMT</pubDate>
   <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 03:19:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
   <copyright>gamblingteachers.com</copyright>
   <item>
    <title>Triple Double Video Poker lesson</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/triple-double.html</link>
    <description>Where else in VP land can you win 4000 coins for a Royal or 4 Aces with a kicker of 2, 3 or 4?
&lt;br&gt;Only with Triple Double Bonus VP as explained in this lesson at Gambling Teachers.
&lt;br&gt;Some of the other top pays for this VP version are: 
&lt;br&gt;1) four 2s, 3s and 4s offer a payout of 400 coins.
&lt;br&gt;2) Add a fifth card kicker of an ace, two, three or four to these quads and a 2000 coin payout is yours.
&lt;br&gt;3) 4 Aces without the required fifth card still puts you in the money with 800 coins.
&lt;br&gt;Here is the bad news to offset the top payouts. Three-of-a-kind is reduced 5 coins to a max coin return of only 10 while straights and flushes are similarly decreased.
&lt;br&gt;May all your VP choices turn out to be &lt;i&gt;Royalty&lt;/i&gt; or with this exciting VP game: 
&lt;i&gt;4 Aces + the payday kicker&lt;/i&gt;.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 03:19:10 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Sportsbetting: Baseball Streaks System</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting-baseball.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers provides a 2-part baseball betting system just in time for the season.
&lt;br&gt;Baseball games traditionally provide great value for savvy punters during the entire 
season.
&lt;br&gt;The most common form of betting is on the moneyline for which team is going to win, straight up, not against the run-line or point spread. 
&lt;br&gt;Baseball features another unique dynamic in that even though it is a team sport, it is really about a single player, the pitcher, against another individual player, the batter.
&lt;br&gt;In the age of the Internet, it is not hard to determine how a particular pitcher does against a specific lineup, or at a particular ballpark. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting-baseball2.html&quot;&gt;Baseball Streaks System, Part 2&lt;/a&gt; provides more tips and an overiew, so you can start &lt;i&gt;betting wise.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 02:10:21 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Online Bonus Report at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-bonuses.html</link>
    <description>This Online Bonus Report at Gambling Teachers details the many rewards for players.
&lt;br&gt;A preview of some of the dozen types of bonuses are Sign-up, Loyalty Rewards, Match Bonus, Percentage Bonus, Cash Back and Referral Programs. 
&lt;br&gt;For example, Rewards for Play: 
&lt;br&gt;These online bonuses are unlike deposit-based bonuses.
&lt;br&gt;Some online casinos comp you based on previous play as opposed to the current deposit. 
&lt;br&gt;Two major loyalty programs fall under this heading and include cash back programs and players clubs.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-gambling.html&quot;&gt;Online Gambling Guide&lt;/a&gt;
 at Gambling Teachers will be your guide to play at the best online casinos.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 21:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Blackjack: Who is in Control?</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/blackjack-control.html</link>
    <description>Most blackjack players sometimes feel the casino/dealer is controlling their destiny. How many times can the same dealer draw that one and only card that beats your hand? 
&lt;br&gt;However, you can take control at the tables.
&lt;br&gt;This Gambling Teachers lesson details
 what the casinos controls are and then the players blackjack control. 
&lt;br&gt;Taught in this blackjack lesson are taking control of rules, betting spread, atmosphere and emotions.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/blackjack.html&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Blackjack&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; program presents 26 other lessons to continue your education of this popular game of 21.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 18:24:02 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>More Slots Winners</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/slots-winners-march.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers has published over 300 winning jackpot stories and this post tells the stories of 3 winners.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) And More to Come &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The giant Wheel of Fortune jackpot of $1,273, 783.55 was hit by Boonchoo Novick at Isle of Capri, Biloxi MS during one of her bi-monthly casino visits The Lawton, OK resident selected a 50-cent slot and after her huge haul was asked what her future plans will be, to which she replied, &lt;i&gt;I plan to do more gambling.&lt;/i&gt; 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) 2 Hits in 4 Days&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Normand Roberge, 44, from New Hampshire hit for $257,845. at a quarter Wheel of Fortune located at the Vegas McCarran Airport. After playing only $20. at his favorite machine, while awaiting his flight home, this happy player is the second jackpot hit in 4 days. &lt;i&gt;I have always had a positive attitude about playing and believe someone has to hit it.&lt;/i&gt;, stated Roberge. 
&lt;br&gt;There is no retirement in the future; however, another visit to Vegas is a certainty.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) And She Said &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Blue Water Casino in Parker, AZ was the place for Larry Jackson who won $750,455 on a one-dollar Wheel of Fortune machine.
&lt;br&gt;Jackson, a retiree from Lake Havasu City, Arizona, had taken a day trip to the casino to play his favorite machines. When asked about his plans, Jackson stated, &lt;i&gt;that will be up to the wife.&lt;/i&gt; 
&lt;br&gt;All &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/slots-winners-reviews.html&quot;&gt;Slots Winners&lt;/a&gt; weekly and monthly reports are listed here so you can read more about &lt;i&gt;life-changing wins&lt;/i&gt;.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 18:42:38 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Let It Ride Tips &amp; Strategies at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/let-it-ride-tips.html</link>
    <description>Let It Ride Tips &amp; Strategies is a lesson available at Gambling Teachers and is one of the 10 Fast Track Games Series. 
&lt;br&gt;Let It Ride can be played as a table game and as a slot game. Online, LIR is also known as Poker Parsuit.
&lt;br&gt;This unique card game depends on the players ability to collect a paying hand and when to Let It Ride.
&lt;br&gt;Your first betting decision is determined by: 
&lt;br&gt;a)    Pair of Tens or better
&lt;br&gt;b)    Possible Straight of 3-4-5 suited or higher. 
&lt;br&gt;Possible Straight of A-2-3 or 2-3-4 suited should not be considered for this betting decision.
&lt;br&gt;c)    Possible Straight from three suited cards with one or two gaps and/or high card(s).
Examples are 9-10-Q and 8-10-Q.
&lt;br&gt;Read More LIR Tips by following this post link.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 05:50:54 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Roulette Wheel Quiz Challenge</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/roulette-wheel.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers invites you to &lt;i&gt;spin and challenge&lt;/i&gt; the wheel with one or both of the specially-created Roulette Quiz at the site.
&lt;br&gt;Here are 3 questions from the Roulette Wheel Quiz
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) Which is the correct payout for a Split Roulette bet?&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Wagering on two numbers at once. An inside bet.
&lt;br&gt;A.    Pays 8 to 1.
&lt;br&gt;B.    Pays 11 to 1.
&lt;br&gt;C.    Pays 17 to 1.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) Which is the correct payout for a Corner bet? &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Wagering on four numbers at once that pays 8 to 1 for a win.
&lt;br&gt;Alternate terms are Square Bet or Quarter Bet.
&lt;br&gt;A.    Pays 5 to 1.  
&lt;br&gt;B.    Pays 8 to 1. 
&lt;br&gt;C.    Pays 11 to 1. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) The en prison rule where your bet is &lt;i&gt;captured&lt;/i&gt; for the next spin reduces the casino edge further to ? &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A.    To 1.1   
&lt;br&gt;B.    To 1.35
&lt;br&gt;C.    To 1.43 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/roulette-quiz.html&quot;&gt;Roulette Quiz #2&lt;/a&gt; will test your knowledge of the game, its history and the odds so you can &lt;i&gt;spin for profits.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 02:32:20 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Winning Gambling History</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-winners.html</link>
    <description>Casino players will enjoy the history of winning gambling records, runs and greatest legends at Gambling Teachers. 
&lt;br&gt;The history recalls the games of Blackjack,
 Baccarat and Poker.
&lt;br&gt;Gambling legends include Kerry Packer,
 Archie Karas, Ken Uston and the &lt;i&gt;million dollar bum.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Enjoy your read and may all casino players aspire to these heights.
&lt;br&gt;Also, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-gambling.html&quot;&gt;Online Gambling Guide&lt;/a&gt; will provide tips, strategies and online winning stories for those casino players who prefer to play via www.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 18:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! 2-Button Share design at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html</link>
    <description>If you want to share the &lt;i&gt;Learn to Win&lt;/i&gt; lessons and programs taught by pros at your Facebook or Twitter, GamblingTs has a new 2-button tool just for you. 
&lt;br&gt;This share resource can be found at the bottom of each page at the site.
&lt;br&gt;Click the link that states &lt;i&gt;Enjoy this page? Please pay it forward. Here&#39;s how... &lt;/i&gt; to add a link to your site, blog or personal page. 
&lt;br&gt;At GamblingTeachers.com, we are attentive about getting the word out about the free programs, lessons and add-ons offered; however, we ask your assistance and thank you for the support.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 06:41:50 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Blackjack Strategy: Right or Wrong?</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/blackjack-strategy.html</link>
    <description>At Gambling Teachers, you will learn that basic blackjack strategy is geared to maximizing wins and minimizing losses -- of money, not hands. 
&lt;br&gt;Sometimes utilizing basic strategy will actually lose you more hands and sometimes what &lt;i&gt;seems wrong&lt;/i&gt; is indeed the right move.
&lt;br&gt;For example, take the hand of Ace-7, a soft 18, against a dealers upcard of 6.
&lt;br&gt;If you stand with the hand, you will win more decisions than if you double the hand. An 18 is a strong hand against a dealers 6.
&lt;br&gt;If you double down, you can only improve your hand by receiving an ace, 2, or 3; if you get a 10 it does not improve it and merely takes the dealers possible bust card, but receiving a 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9 worsens the hand.
&lt;br&gt;So you have a soft 18 and you double down and get a 4. There you are with a 12 and twice as much money out! 
&lt;br&gt;Does this make sense? Maybe it does; maybe it does not.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 09:43:47 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Poker Dice Lesson at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-dice.html</link>
    <description>Poker Dice is one of the most famous dice games. This lesson at Gambling Teachers details dice history, rules, scoring and strategies. 
&lt;br&gt;Poker Dice Rules: A standard dice used is a six-sided cube made of plastic.
&lt;br&gt;The dice display representations of playing cards instead of numbers. Each of the six sides represent Ace, King, Queen, Jack, Ten and Nine that are used to form a Poker hand.
&lt;br&gt;The values in order of rank are Ace, King, Queen, Jack, Ten and Nine.
&lt;br&gt;The object of the game is to make the best poker hand combination from rolls of the Poker Dice. Every player antes up into a pot before rolling.
&lt;br&gt;Each player then rolls five dice at their individual turns and tries to get the best combination with maximum points in different rows.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps.html&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Craps&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
 program is the site location for Poker Dice and 2 other favorite and diverse dice games--Sic Bo and Yahtzee.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 19:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Casino Rules &amp; Lingo</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/casino-rules.html</link>
    <description>This lesson at Gambling Teachers provides
 casino rules and lingo/language of the casino.
&lt;br&gt;Casinos have their own rules, lingo and culture. If you dont want to feel like an unwanted foreigner, you have to understand the language and rules and then you must assimilate.
&lt;br&gt;The Buy-in is discussed at this lesson as are Betting procedures.
&lt;br&gt;Casino chips come in all sorts of denominations and colors. Usually, $1 chip are white or blue; $5 chips are red; $25 chips are green; $100 chips are black; $500 chips are purple; $1,000 chips are gold or gray, and $2,000 chips are orange. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-strategies-tips.html#termsall&quot;&gt;Gambling Tips &amp; Strategies&lt;/a&gt; will get you into the &lt;i&gt;casino speak&lt;/i&gt; mode with 12 lessons that provide casino gambling terms, lingo, jargon and phrases for all the popular games.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 18:24:21 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Double Double VP Excitement</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/double-double-videopoker.html</link>
    <description>&lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Video Poker&lt;/i&gt; at Gambling Teachers offers 18 lessons for specific VP versions, however, one of the most popular is Double Double VP.
&lt;br&gt;Its easy to see the attraction for Double Double VP, in that four aces with a kicker (fifth card) of a 2, 3 or 4 produce a nice payday of 2000 coins or half a Royal Flush.
&lt;br&gt;Also, an increased payout is yours for four-of-a-kind 2s 3s and 4s completed by a fifth card of an ace, two, three or four.
&lt;br&gt;This lesson at Gambling Teachers includes an illustrated paytable and strategies.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/videopoker.html&quot;&gt; Learn VP Program &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt; lessons teach VP strategies, Q&amp;A, tips, terms and 2 quiz.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 03:01:28 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Craps Quiz at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps-game-quiz.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers offers 2 Craps Quiz: basic and advanced at the Free Learning Center.
 Here are 3 questions from the Basic Quiz
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) Which of these statements is incorrect in Craps? &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A. The Place Bet on a 6 or 8 has a casino advantage of 1.5.  
&lt;br&gt;B.  6 or 8 Place Bet is the same as the Big 6 or 8. 
&lt;br&gt;C.  Big 6 or 8 wager is even money and casino edge is 9.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) What does the term Wrong Bettor mean in Craps?   &lt;/b&gt; 
&lt;br&gt;A.  Player who bets The Horn.   
&lt;br&gt;B.  Player who bets Dont Pass--Dont Come.
&lt;br&gt;C.  Player who bets the Big 6 and 8. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) What does the term Hook mean in Craps?&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A.  Imaginary line that separates players 3 and 4.
&lt;br&gt;B.  Device used by the Stickman.
&lt;br&gt;C.  The combination of 3 and 4 on a dice equaling 7.     
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps-quiz.html&quot;&gt; Craps Advanced Quiz&lt;/a&gt;
 will test your knowledge of numbers and strategies for this dice game.
Can you hear the roar of the crowd?</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 19:38:11 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Your Gambling Plan of Attack</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-plan.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers suggests you create a gambling plan of attack. 
&lt;br&gt;Some players go into casinos with a plan; others go in with a few bucks and a dream of riches.
&lt;br&gt;Who is more likely to come out with the riches --- or at least with part of their bankroll intact? The player with a plan, of course.
&lt;br&gt;This lesson lists a few things to consider before your day at the casino online of off:
&lt;br&gt;1) Learn the games before you play.
 A little homework goes a long way in helping to cut the odds against you at casino games. Learn basic strategy and know the rules and best bets. 
&lt;br&gt;No matter your game of choice, Gambling Teachers is sure to offer assistance taught by gambling pros at the Free Learning Center.
&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-strategies-tips.html&quot;&gt; Gambling Strategies &amp; Tips&lt;/a&gt; is an excellent starting point. Also, this program provides the lingo-terms series of 12 lessons.
&lt;br&gt; Sounds like a plan, yes?</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 05:19:56 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Poker Lessons, Part 2 at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/learn-poker-games.html</link>
    <description>There are plenty of poker games to explore at this GT program.
&lt;br&gt; Learn about Stud Poker, Caribbean Stud, 3-Card Poker, Pai Gow Poker, Let it Ride, European Games of Baccarat, Punto Banco and Chemin de Fer, 12 Other Versions with Red Dog, Rummy plus tournaments.
&lt;br&gt;This poker jargon will get your started.
&lt;br&gt;Monster: you have an almost certain winning hand here.
&lt;br&gt;Rush: poker lingo for a big win quickly--truly a rush.
&lt;br&gt;Sailboats: poker jargon for a pair of fours starting hand.
&lt;br&gt;Snap Off: you call the bluffer and beat him/her with a not-so-hot-hand--a sweet deal.
&lt;br&gt;Check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-software-reviews-tournaments.html&quot;&gt; 7 Poker Software Reviews&lt;/a&gt; that include individual games of Holdem, Omaha and Stud followed by 3 tournament reviews.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 17:19:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Poker Lessons in 2 Parts at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers offers an extensive &lt;i&gt;Learn Poker Program&lt;/i&gt; in 2 Parts.
&lt;br&gt;The first part/program includes lessons for General Strategies, Holdem, Omaha, Hi-Lo Games and Wild Card Games.
&lt;br&gt;We begin with some Poker Lingo:
&lt;br&gt;Aces Wired or Bullets: poker lingo for pair of aces in the hole--a beautiful site.
&lt;br&gt;Berry Patch: poker lingo for a smooth and easy game.
&lt;br&gt;Buy the Pot: poker strategy games term for a strong wager that likely puts other players out of the game.
&lt;br&gt;Fishhooks: poker strategy games and terms for the 4 jacks in the deck.
&lt;br&gt;Glimmer: that&#39;s the cash, money or moolah.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-gambling.html&quot;&gt; Online Gaming Guide &lt;/a&gt; presents 12 Poker lessons to explore before entering the online poker world.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 17:36:50 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>For passionate video gamers by gamerisms</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html#For-passionate-video-gamers-by-gamerisms</link>
    <description>&lt;object style=&quot;height: 390px; width: 640px&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/v/gSYmOAzP72c?version=3&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowFullScreen&quot; value=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;always&quot;&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/v/gSYmOAzP72c?version=3&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; allowScriptAccess=&quot;always&quot; width=&quot;440&quot; height=&quot;290&quot;&gt;&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;gamerisms offers a second video and link to discover the unique language of video games and gamers.
&lt;!--b62038e590c44c4d8867477778c31aa9--&gt;</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 14:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>New Video for gamerisms</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html#New-Video-for-gamerisms</link>
    <description>&lt;object width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;385&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/v/Qb3ozmgIBUw?fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot;&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowFullScreen&quot; value=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowscriptaccess&quot; value=&quot;always&quot;&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/v/Qb3ozmgIBUw?fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;always&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; width=&quot;440&quot; height=&quot;285&quot;&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;gamerisms shows off a new video for the defining games glossary &amp; quiz site dedicated to sports, casino, skill and video game players.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 19:50:14 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Video Poker Online Versions</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/video-poker-online.html</link>
    <description>This Video Poker Online lesson at Gambling Teachers begins with the classic versions also available at land-based casinos.
&lt;br&gt;Examples are Jacks or Better, Deuces Wild, Joker Poker and Pick em Poker.
&lt;br&gt;This GT lesson then moves to selections that are unique to online gambling.
&lt;br&gt;Examples are Aces &amp; Eights, 2 Ways Royal, Power Poker Options, Superjax and Megajacks.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 22:33:14 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Talking Rummy at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/rummy.html</link>
    <description>This Introduction to Rummy Games lesson at Gambling Teachers describes rules, strategies, history and scoring.
&lt;br&gt;Popular variations of rummy include:
 Knock, Gin, Oklahoma Gin, Kaluki, Poker Rum and Continental Rummy.
&lt;br&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/rummy-quiz.html&quot;&gt; Rummy Quiz&lt;/a&gt; follows this lesson to test your knowledge of the game.
&lt;br&gt;Both Rummy lessons are now found at  
&lt;i&gt;Learn Poker 2&lt;/i&gt; program.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 19:48:39 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! Aristocrat Slots 2011 Preview</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/aristocrat-slots-2011.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers presents Aristocrat Slots 2011, part 5 that completes the series of slot games previews as presented by five innovative slot makers--Atronic, Bally, Aristocrat, IGT and Wms Gaming.
&lt;br&gt;Some highlights are: 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kingmaker&lt;/i&gt; has created a humorous social media campaign, starring Bigfoot, to drive Aristocrats Reel Tall Tales video slot game. 
&lt;br&gt;New game categories include the advanced technology of Mega Pay, Remix and Win Your Way. Available on player-favorite game titles: More Hearts and More Chilli, in Mega Pay. 
&lt;br&gt;When these multi-games play during the free games feature, players get a Mega Pay, where one game can become four games.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 17:16:27 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! Bally Slots 2011 Preview</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/bally-slots-2011.html</link>
    <description>Bally Slots 2011 lesson is part 3 of the 5 part series: Slots Previews as reported by Gambling Teachers.
&lt;br&gt;Bally 2011 slots include newer versions of Betty Boop, Playboy and Cash Wizard Pro.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;u&gt;U Spin Feature:&lt;/u&gt; with this feature during bonus sequences, the player gets to touch the screen and spin the bonus wheel just as if it were an actual physical wheel.
&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Bally will introduce Hot Pick, the follow-on title to Cash Spin. 
&lt;br&gt;See lesson at Gambling Teachers for much more Bally 2011.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 18:09:55 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! Atronic Slots 2011 Preview</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/atronic-slots-2011.html</link>
    <description>Atronic Slots 2011 lesson is part 2 of the 5 part series: Slots Previews as reported by Gambling Teachers.
&lt;br&gt;Atronic and Spielos 2011 line-up includes the launch of a new cabinet and product range, as well as exciting linked, progressives, and community games, player-tested cabinets, proven core game titles, three hot new family brands, and flexible systems solutions.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 18:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! IGT Slots 2011 Preview</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/igt-slots-2011.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers presents a 5-part series
 of 2011 slot previews. 
&lt;br&gt;First up is IGT or International Game Technology followed by Atronic, Bally, Aristocrat and Wms Gaming.
&lt;br&gt;This peek at the future of slot games is always exciting and anticipated by slot players. &lt;br&gt;These newer slots were introduced at Global Gaming Expo (G2E) in November/2010.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 20:54:36 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>WMS slots 2011, part 4 previews newer casino slot games for
players from Wms Gaming</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/wms-slots-2011.html</link>
    <description>WMS slots 2011, Williams Gaming previews newer slot games at casinos, part 4 of 5 as reported by gambling teachers</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 20:40:45 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! VP Online Strategy: Double Bonus</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/video-poker-online-strategy.html</link>
    <description>This Video Poker Online Strategy lesson at Gambling Teachers focuses on the Double Bonus version. 
&lt;br&gt;There are detailed strategies to make correct decisions for straights, flushes and 4 Ace possibilities. 
&lt;br&gt; When it comes to making a decision for  an 800-coin jackpot=4 Aces, we make a play that would be regarded as very strange in Jacks or Better.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/videopoker.html&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Video Poker&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; program now boasts 34 lessons
 to help players &lt;i&gt;on their way to Royalty&lt;/i&gt;.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Paigow without cards</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/paigow-game.html</link>
    <description>This Paigow Game lesson describes the version without cards and brings the number of lessons about paigow to a total of 5 found at the Gambling Teachers, &lt;i&gt;Learn Poker 2&lt;/i&gt; program. 
&lt;br&gt;Instead of cards, the game is played with domino tiles and dice.
&lt;br&gt;Paigow simply means to make nine, implying that if you intend to win, you have to get a tile score as close to 9 as possible. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/learn-poker-games.html&quot;&gt;Poker 2&lt;/a&gt; is where you will find all Paigow and other poker lessons + tournaments at the GT Learning Center.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 19:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Skill Game News</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html#Skill-Game-News</link>
    <description>ChChChanges at Gambling Teachers for the Skill Games program. 
&lt;br&gt;Most of the program lessons have been moved to the gamerisms.com site to compliment the extensive skill games glossary area. 
&lt;br&gt;Some lessons for Paigow, rummy, 3 Dice Games as announced and 3 Quiz units will remain.
&lt;br&gt;All previous lessons are redirected and available at GT or skill gamerisms where this post link will take you.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 22:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>3 Dice Game Lessons added to Learn Craps</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps.html#dicegames</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers has added 3 dice game lessons to the &lt;i&gt;Learn Craps&lt;/i&gt; program that will be of interest to players who &lt;i&gt;love to roll dem bones&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;The unique dice games of Sic Bo, Poker Dice and Yahtzee lessons now appear along with the most popular dice game worldwide--Craps.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sic-bo-dice-game.html&quot;&gt;Sic Bo&lt;/a&gt; game lesson includes rules, strategies and 2 betting charts for big bet and small bet. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-dice.html&quot;&gt;Poker Dice&lt;/a&gt; game lesson brings you history, rules and scoring details.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/yahtzee-dice-game.html&quot;&gt;Yahtzee,&lt;/a&gt; the classic dice game for all ages has rules and stats probabilities for this game lesson.
&lt;br&gt;We invite you to view and share these dice game diversions.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 20:51:04 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Slots Winners: The Sequel</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/slots-winners.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers has reported over 300 slots wins and revisits 3 of those winning stories:
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) Jersey Educator: A New Millionaire&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;A 56 year-old special education teacher from Jersey hit it big with a $1,577,661 MegaJackpot at a nickel Wheel of Fortune slot at Harrahs Atlantic City. The anonymous millionaire went with her favorite slot while visiting AC with a friend. The huge strike astonished the winner, but she stated her life would not change except for repairs to her current home and a new car.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2) 3 Coins will do it&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Penni Greene from Willingboro, NJ hit for $472,435 at a quarter Jeopardy progressive after playing only 3 coins. &lt;i&gt;I am really surprised,&lt;/i&gt; said Greene. &lt;i&gt;I frequently visit Borgata, it is my favorite place to play. I really enjoy the people and the machines are always fun.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3) Trade Show Visit Produces a Huge Payday&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Shi Chul Kum of Flower Mound, TX. visiting a Vegas trade show was the shocked winner of $3,080,610. at a Wheel of Fortune progressive slot. Kum had spent only $40 at the 50-cent Megajackpot game at the Venetian Resort Hotel Casino. &lt;i&gt;I was just passing through the casino after leaving the trade show and I thought I would try my luck,&lt;/i&gt; said the new millionaire. &lt;i&gt;When I saw what I won, I went totally blank. I could not think.&lt;/i&gt;  Future plans include a cash infusion for his business.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/slots-winners-reviews.html&quot;&gt;Slots 2&lt;/a&gt; at GT lists Slots Winners, Millionaires, Reviews and links to Online Winners along with
 previews. You can &lt;i&gt;pick and click&lt;/i&gt; your way through&lt;i&gt; lots o slots &lt;/i&gt; info. Enjoy your read!</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 19:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Talking Poker Tournaments</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-history-tournaments.html</link>
    <description>This lesson at gambling teachers details the history of poker that in turn evolved into the excitement of tournaments played online and off.
&lt;br&gt;Here is a list of 5 of the better known Poker Tournaments in the US:
&lt;br&gt;World Series of Poker, Las Vegas 
&lt;br&gt;Shooting Star, San Jose California
&lt;br&gt;California State Poker Championship
&lt;br&gt;Legends of Poker
&lt;br&gt;World Poker Finals
&lt;br&gt;Some of the largest and most recognized poker names online are: William Hill, Ladbrokes, Titan, Full Tilt Poker and Paddy Power.
&lt;br&gt;This lesson offers up more than enough reasons to &lt;i&gt;shuffle up and deal!&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-gambling.html&quot;&gt; the GT Online Gaming Guide
&lt;/a&gt; in 4 parts to include Fast Track Gambling Tips will benefit new and veteran casino players.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 04:29:32 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Craps Strategy: 1, 2 Punch</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps-strategy.html</link>
    <description>This &lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Craps&lt;/i&gt; lesson at Gambling Teachers explores the craps strategy known as the 1, 2 Punch.
&lt;br&gt;Craps is unique among casino games. It is the only game in the casino where the house gives the player the dice and says, &lt;i&gt;Here, beat us if you can.!&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Craps can be divided into two separate games. There is the mathematical game based on the probabilities inherent in two six-sided dice and there is the physical game where people roll the dice.
&lt;br&gt;If you are a novice craps player and you look at the layout, it can be baffling and offering a gazillion bets, mostly bad.
&lt;br&gt;Yet, stripped of its makeup, language and dress, craps is plain and simple. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/horn-bets.html&quot;&gt;Horn Bets &lt;/a&gt; to include strategies and systems follows the 1, 2 Punch lesson at the Gambling Teachers Free Learning Center.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 02:16:57 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Caribbean Stud Poker: Advanced Lesson</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/caribbean-stud-poker.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers provides basic and advanced lessons for Caribbean Stud Poker at the learning center. 
&lt;br&gt; The advanced level requires additional effort, with dozens of exceptions to the basic strategy of drawing to hands with no pairs.
&lt;br&gt;The best hands to hold are in this order: &lt;br&gt;4-card royal, 4-card straight flush, 4-card straight, 4-card open straight, 3-card royal, 3-card straight flush to include inside and double-inside draws, 
&lt;br&gt;Also, 3-card flush or 4-card inside straight. Or hold 3 highest cards.
&lt;br&gt;Advanced strategies follow.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-games-online.html#cstud&quot;&gt;Basic Caribbean Stud strategy&lt;/a&gt; and rules are taught at this lesson. This poker version online is also known as Cyber Stud.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 04:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Talking Bingo Rules &amp; Strategies</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/bingo-strategies.html</link>
    <description>This lesson at Gambling Teachers talks Bingo Strategies &amp; Rules.
&lt;br&gt;The game has always been a best bet because, except progressive games, there is always a winner for each game, unlike a lottery. 
&lt;br&gt;Two strategies from the lesson are:
&lt;br&gt; Listen and react quickly to the called number because if you miss any numbers, you are reducing your chances of a win.
&lt;br&gt; If you play during slow hours at any bingo hall or online, you will increase your odds with fewer players, especially for progressive games. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/bingo-keno.html&quot;&gt; Learn Bingo-Keno &lt;/a&gt; Games Program is the main game page at Gambling Teachers with lessons for 2 games that are considered to be softer gambling bets.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 19:15:16 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Blackjack Surrender Explained + Strategy</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/blackjack-surrender.html</link>
    <description>The Blackjack Surrender lesson at Gambling Teachers explains this playing option and offers strategy tips.
&lt;br&gt;If you know when to use the surrender option correctly, it can be an advantage. On the other hand, if you misuse the option it is like throwing money down the drain. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blackjack Surrender: &lt;/b&gt;after a player receives initial two cards, the player may, at his/her discretion, surrender the hand. If he decides to surrender, he indicates this to the dealer. 
&lt;br&gt;The result is the player forfeits his/her chance to play out the hand and the casino keeps one-half of the players bet. 
&lt;br&gt;The lesson continues with strategy tips and percentage play.
&lt;br&gt;GT suggests&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/baccarat-play.html&quot;&gt; Baccarat &amp; Punto Banco Rules, &lt;/a&gt; two exciting casino games played online and off. If you like blackjack, you will probably like these games.
.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Online Free Play Guide</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-free.html</link>
    <description>The majority of online players have opted to play for free, but may not have considered all the advantages. This lesson guide at Gambling Teachers details online free play.
&lt;br&gt;Free or practice play including online poker free-rolls is a casino luxury that most often goes unappreciated.
&lt;br&gt;It is more of a fantastic opportunity to explore what is available, and to learn the many free casino games with zero risk involved.
&lt;br&gt;It gives online players the chance to test strategies that are both proven, and theoretical, learn the basics of games that they are not familiar with or to simply have fun knowing there is no consequence no matter what they decide to do. 
&lt;br&gt;Want to play that favorite game at a max bet of $200 a spin? Go for it!
&lt;br&gt;The free play is not just for novice players though. They are a wonderful resource for gamblers of all skill levels.
&lt;br&gt;Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-casinos.html&quot;&gt; Rating Online Casinos&lt;/a&gt; presents 20 questions and a scoring system at Gambling Teachers that will be your guide to play at the best online casinos.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 03:23:06 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Gambling Math with Wild Examples</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-math.html</link>
    <description>This lesson at Gambling Teachers begins with basic casino math and continues with wild examples of outlandish wins and horrendous losses.
&lt;br&gt;Gambling Math can tell us what our average expected loss or win will be at each and every game by plugging our betting levels into a very simple formula: Average Bet x Speed of Game x Hours Played x House Edge = Expected Win/Loss.
&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, owing to the streaky, freaky nature of chance, the above formula really would not tell you if you were going to lose or whether you would win a bundle, or a single bet, because averages are, well, averages.
&lt;br&gt;Therefore, winning and losing at casino games rarely match the average expectation on a given evening because wild, weird, and wonderful things can happen, as the following examples demonstrate.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-faq.html&quot;&gt; Gambling FAQ &lt;/a&gt; that includes 16 Questions about casino gambling where GT supplies the answers follows the Gambling Math lesson.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 02:19:04 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Twin Poker Picks at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers presents 2 poker programs with over 60 lessons taught by gambling pros. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot; http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker.html &quot;&gt;1) How to Play Poker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt; program provides General poker lessons plus Holdem, Omaha and Wild Card game lessons.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/learn-poker-games.html&quot;&gt;2) Learn Poker Games&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt; offers lessons for Stud Poker, Caribbean Stud, 3-Card Poker, Pai Gow Poker, Let it Ride, European Games of Baccarat, Punto Banco, Chemin de Fer and Other Versions: 12 Games plus Tournaments. 
&lt;br&gt;Let&#39;s Shuffle Up and Deal!</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 17:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Slots Types Updated at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/slots-introduction.html</link>
    <description>Now that Community play or Multi-player slots are a common sight on the casino floor, it&#39;s time to take another look at slot types available for play. 
&lt;br&gt;In this lesson, the four main types of slots at land-based casinos along with examples are described. 
&lt;br&gt;4 types or groups of slots:   
&lt;br&gt;1.  Basic slots with a single payline and constant jackpot.   
&lt;br&gt;2.  Progressives that offer an ever-growing jackpot.   
&lt;br&gt;3.  Bonus Added Slots. Additional features including multi-spins, 5 reels, multi-lines, bonus games, free spins and nudge-hold. 
&lt;br&gt;4. Community Play or Multi-Player Concept setup to accommodate several players, all of whom can qualify for the top jackpot bonus round and gather credits separately at their station. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-slots.html&quot;&gt;Online Slots Strategies&lt;/a&gt; is a recommended follow-up lesson that describes online slots types, examples and strategies.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 21:15:15 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Types of sportsbetting: specific games</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/Gambling-Teachers-blog.html#Types-of-sportsbetting:-specific-games</link>
    <description>If you think you can bet on almost anything when it comes to the wide world of sports, you would be correct.
&lt;br&gt;Gambling Teachers and gamerisms provide examples for types of sportbetting for specific games. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sport=American Football:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;--First to 3 Touchdowns: sport game bet on the team that will be the first to score 3 touchdowns.
&lt;br&gt;--Kick Off: wager on which team will kick off the game.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sport=Basketball:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;--Highest Quarter: wagering on the quarter in a game that will have the highest score.
&lt;br&gt;--Largest Lead: sport bet as to which team will have the largest point lead during a game excluding overtime.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sport=Hockey:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;--First Period: sport games betting based on the score of the first period in the hockey game.
&lt;br&gt;--Total Assists: betting on the number of assists made by a player or team
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sport=Soccer/Football:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;--Last Player to Score: betting on the player who will be the last to score in a soccer match during regulation 90 minutes of play.
&lt;br&gt;--Last to Score: wagering on the team who will be the last to score during a regulation game.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sport=Tennis:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;--Aces: betting on the player who serves the most aces during a match.
&lt;br&gt;--First Break: sport game bet for the first player to break their challenger&#39;s serve to win the match.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamerisms.com/sportsbetting-sportsbook-glossary.html&quot;&gt;sportsbetting glossary &amp; quiz&lt;/a&gt; at gamerisms offers a comprehensive glossary with sport betting terms and types of bets. 
&lt;br&gt;Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting.html&quot;&gt;Learn Sportsbetting&lt;/a&gt; program at Gambling Teachers offers 12 lessons taught by 3 gaming pros.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 17:49:58 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Blackjack: Player vs Casino Favorable Rules</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/play-blackjack.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers asks the question: &lt;i&gt;Of all the casino games, why learn to play blackjack? What makes it different from any other casino game? &lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;For one, the odds in blackjack are not constant. They keep changing from one hand to the next depending on the cards that have been played.
&lt;br&gt;The bottom line is that blackjack is a game of skill not just luck.
&lt;br&gt;Secondly, not all games are created equal. You will often find different playing rules from one casino to the next and even within the same casino. 
&lt;br&gt;Some rules are more player-favorable and others favor the casino. 
&lt;br&gt;Its this mix of rules that ultimately determines the casinos overall edge and whether the game is good or bad.
&lt;br&gt;With this lesson at Gambling Teachers, 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/blackjack.html&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Blackjack&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; program,  there is a summary of the rules that favor the player and those that favor the casino.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 19:30:09 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Bingo Quiz Preview at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/bingo-quiz.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers has a fun and challenging Bingo Quiz with 10 questions and answers.
&lt;br&gt;Here is a preview:
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1)&lt;/b&gt; What does the term &lt;i&gt;Blackout &lt;/i&gt;mean? 
&lt;br&gt;A.  Black dauber used on a Bingo card.
&lt;br&gt;B.  Bingo Balls stop &lt;i&gt;tumbling&lt;/i&gt; in the cage.
&lt;br&gt;C.  Bingo win that covers all numbers on the card.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2)&lt;/b&gt; What is a &lt;i&gt;Hardway&lt;/i&gt; win? 
&lt;br&gt;A.  A win with one line not using the free space. 
&lt;br&gt;B.  A win with two lines. 
&lt;br&gt;C.  A win with two lines not using the free space.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3)&lt;/b&gt; How do you say 25 in Brit Bingo Lingo?
&lt;br&gt;A.  Its Alive. 
&lt;br&gt;B.  Duck and Dive.
&lt;br&gt;C.  Take that Drive.
&lt;br&gt;A listing of all &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/bingo-keno.html&quot;&gt;Bingo &amp; Keno&lt;/a&gt; lessons offered at Gambling Teachers is available at this link.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 18:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! 7 Poker Software Reviews</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/poker-software-reviews-tournaments.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers presents 7 poker software reviews for players looking for resources to improve their game.
&lt;br&gt;Poker software is an excellent resource for new or veteran players alike. It offers the best training, simulation of the games along with valuable stats for your game and your opponents.
&lt;br&gt;The 7 poker software reviews are listed in order of individual games of Holdem, Omaha and Stud followed by 3 tournament reviews.
&lt;br&gt;Wilson software poker series for Holdem, Omaha and Stud poker are up first.
&lt;br&gt;The 3 Tourney reviews are DD Tournament Poker,  Poker Tournament Manager and Tournament Director.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Be the best poker player you can be!&lt;/i&gt; with this helpful lesson at Gambling Teachers.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 20:13:21 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Table Talk &amp;  10 Craps Commandments</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/craps-table-talk.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers begins this lesson with 5 continuous dialogues at the craps table.
&lt;br&gt;The conversation moves quickly and is guaranteed to bring a knowing smile to all players. 
&lt;br&gt;The 10 Craps Commandments complete the article and here are 3 examples.
&lt;br&gt; Never push your way into a game next to a person who is shooting. If you bump him, you know what will happen and you just know what big guy will be after you.
&lt;br&gt;Never say the word &lt;i&gt;seven&lt;/i&gt; at a craps table. If you do, it will appear.
&lt;br&gt; Never dangle your hands over the craps table because if the dice hit them, the &lt;i&gt;seven&lt;/i&gt; will appear and so will that big guy mentioned earlier.
&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamerisms.com/craps-game-glossary.html&quot;&gt;craps game glossary&lt;/a&gt; at gamerisms.com in 3 parts extends the table talk with terms, lingo and jargon for the language of craps.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 01:44:22 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Baseball Streaks Systems at Gambling Teachers</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting-baseball2.html</link>
    <description>Part 2 of this Baseball System at Gambling Teachers offers 10 quick tips. &lt;br&gt;Here are a couple to begin your &lt;i&gt;streak&lt;/i&gt;.
&lt;br&gt;1) Always have more than one bookmaker, whether live or online, at your disposal, especially when betting on the money-line, so you can get the best possible odds.
&lt;br&gt;2) Do your homework before betting on the run-line, carefully analyze the pitcher and his past history against the opposing batters.
&lt;br&gt;Also check your team&#39;s recent run production and margin of victory history. Some teams live and die by 1-run games, while other clubs habitually play comparatively few 1-run games.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting-baseball.html&quot;&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt; of this baseball system at &lt;i&gt;Learn Sportsbetting&lt;/i&gt; offers in-depth details.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 05:44:08 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Gambling Terms Quiz Challenge</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-terms-quiz.html</link>
    <description>This quiz challenge at Gambling Teachers is designed to increase your gambling vocabulary with the added benefit of impressing your playing buddies.
&lt;br&gt;Some of these terms or lingo have a long history and will surely add some fun to your next casino experience.
&lt;br&gt;Below are 2 quiz questions about casino players. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1) &lt;/b&gt;Player who is a George does what? 
&lt;br&gt;A.  George is a generous tipper.
&lt;br&gt;B.  George is a lurker who watches a game like blackjack, also known as Curious George.
&lt;br&gt;C.  George plays craps only.  
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2)&lt;/b&gt; What is a Dept. of the Interior Player?
&lt;br&gt;A.  Player who has inside information about the race/bet.
&lt;br&gt;B.  Poker player who has bagged an inside straight.    
&lt;br&gt;C.  Craps player who makes an inside bet.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;View &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-quiz-series.html&quot;&gt; All GT Quiz Series&lt;/a&gt; that includes Table, Slots, Sportsbetting and Skill games.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 17:09:39 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>10 Rules for Successful Online Play</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/gambling-online.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers talks &lt;i&gt;Learn to Win&lt;/i&gt; tips and strategy for online play in this lesson.
&lt;br&gt;The odds are almost always stacked against you whether gambling online or off. The games require a lot of skill, self-discipline, resolve and guile to be successful at it.
&lt;br&gt;You certainly cannot always expect to win of course, no matter how well you play but you dont always have to lose either.
&lt;br&gt;By simply making an extra effort to learn some basic rules to be successful and make them part of your play, you can increase your odds of winning significantly.
&lt;br&gt;Gambling Teachers is the best resource online for &lt;br&gt;Rule #1: Learn First, Play Later.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You can read and learn all 10 rules and then continue your education with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/online-gambling.html&quot;&gt; GT Online Gaming Guide&lt;/a&gt; offering 25 lessons in 4 parts to include 10 Fast Track Gambling Series.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 15:41:11 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>NEW! Aces and Eights Blackjack Strategy</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/aces-and-eights-blackjack.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers has added a new lesson to &lt;i&gt;Learn to Play Blackjack&lt;/i&gt; program.
&lt;br&gt;Several example hands and strategies about how to play aces and eights blackjack together or as pairs of 8s or aces are detailed.
&lt;br&gt;For example, take a hand of 16. No matter how you slice it, a hand of 16 is a rotten hand. Hit it and you will bust over 60 percent of the time; stand and the dealer will have to bust. &lt;br&gt;You will be a big loser when you stand as well, around 70 percent of the time.
&lt;br&gt;But a 16 composed of two 8s is an entirely different matter. Read More...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 02:33:43 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
   <item>
    <title>Sportsbetting Quiz and Lessons at GamblingTs</title>
    <link>http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting-quiz.html</link>
    <description>Gambling Teachers provides a quiz and 12 &lt;i&gt;Learn to Win&lt;/i&gt;  sportsbetting lessons at the site.
&lt;br&gt;Here are 3 of the 10 questions that will test your knowledge and tickle your smile meter. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;1)&lt;/b&gt; What does the term Ante Post mean?
&lt;br&gt;A. A wager placed on an event against another bettor.
&lt;br&gt;B. Betting that is placed 1 or more days before the date of the event.
&lt;br&gt;C. A bettor who is against wooden poles.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;2)&lt;/b&gt; What does the punters&#39;     term, Chalkeater mean?
&lt;br&gt;A. A punter who wants to write on the blackboard.
&lt;br&gt;B. Lingo for a punter with bad habits.
&lt;br&gt;C. Lingo for someone who bets only on favorites.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;3)&lt;/b&gt; What does Odd-Even refer to?
&lt;br&gt;A. Names of the twins who operate the new craps table.
&lt;br&gt;B. Betting on whether total goals will result in an even or an odd number.
&lt;br&gt;C. The numbered groups of punters that are divided for a certain sporting event.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamblingteachers.com/sportsbetting.html&quot;&gt;Learn Sportsbetting&lt;/a&gt; program offers lessons about sportsbook, exchanges, terms, online betting, horseracing, baseball and sportsbetting bankroll.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 14:48:07 GMT</pubDate>
   </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
